<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<office:document-content xmlns:office="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:office:1.0" xmlns:style="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:style:1.0" xmlns:text="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:text:1.0" xmlns:table="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:table:1.0" xmlns:draw="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:drawing:1.0" xmlns:fo="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:xsl-fo-compatible:1.0" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:meta="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:meta:1.0" xmlns:number="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:datastyle:1.0" xmlns:svg="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:svg-compatible:1.0" xmlns:chart="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:chart:1.0" xmlns:dr3d="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:dr3d:1.0" xmlns:math="http://www.w3.org/1998/Math/MathML" xmlns:form="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:form:1.0" xmlns:script="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:script:1.0" xmlns:ooo="http://openoffice.org/2004/office" xmlns:ooow="http://openoffice.org/2004/writer" xmlns:oooc="http://openoffice.org/2004/calc" xmlns:dom="http://www.w3.org/2001/xml-events" xmlns:xforms="http://www.w3.org/2002/xforms" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:rpt="http://openoffice.org/2005/report" xmlns:of="urn:oasis:names:tc:opendocument:xmlns:of:1.2" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" xmlns:grddl="http://www.w3.org/2003/g/data-view#" xmlns:officeooo="http://openoffice.org/2009/office" xmlns:tableooo="http://openoffice.org/2009/table" xmlns:drawooo="http://openoffice.org/2010/draw" xmlns:calcext="urn:org:documentfoundation:names:experimental:calc:xmlns:calcext:1.0" xmlns:loext="urn:org:documentfoundation:names:experimental:office:xmlns:loext:1.0" xmlns:field="urn:openoffice:names:experimental:ooo-ms-interop:xmlns:field:1.0" xmlns:formx="urn:openoffice:names:experimental:ooxml-odf-interop:xmlns:form:1.0" xmlns:css3t="http://www.w3.org/TR/css3-text/" office:version="1.2"><office:scripts/><office:font-face-decls><style:font-face style:name="LatoWeb" svg:font-family="LatoWeb, &apos;Helvetica Neue&apos;, Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif"/><style:font-face style:name="FreeSans1" svg:font-family="FreeSans" style:font-family-generic="swiss"/><style:font-face style:name="Liberation Serif" svg:font-family="&apos;Liberation Serif&apos;" style:font-family-generic="roman" style:font-pitch="variable"/><style:font-face style:name="Liberation Sans" svg:font-family="&apos;Liberation Sans&apos;" style:font-family-generic="swiss" style:font-pitch="variable"/><style:font-face style:name="FreeSans" svg:font-family="FreeSans" style:font-family-generic="system" style:font-pitch="variable"/><style:font-face style:name="Noto Sans CJK SC Regular" svg:font-family="&apos;Noto Sans CJK SC Regular&apos;" style:font-family-generic="system" style:font-pitch="variable"/></office:font-face-decls><office:automatic-styles><style:style style:name="P1" style:family="paragraph" style:parent-style-name="Standard"><style:text-properties fo:font-variant="normal" fo:text-transform="none" fo:color="#2d3b45" style:font-name="LatoWeb" fo:font-size="7pt" fo:letter-spacing="normal" fo:font-style="normal" fo:font-weight="normal" officeooo:rsid="0003e931" officeooo:paragraph-rsid="0003e931"/></style:style><style:style style:name="P2" style:family="paragraph" style:parent-style-name="Standard"><style:text-properties fo:font-variant="normal" fo:text-transform="none" fo:color="#2d3b45" style:font-name="LatoWeb" fo:font-size="7pt" fo:letter-spacing="normal" fo:font-style="normal" fo:font-weight="normal" officeooo:paragraph-rsid="0003e931"/></style:style><style:style style:name="P3" style:family="paragraph" style:parent-style-name="Standard"><style:text-properties fo:font-variant="normal" fo:text-transform="none" fo:color="#2d3b45" style:font-name="LatoWeb" fo:font-size="7pt" fo:letter-spacing="normal" fo:font-style="normal" fo:font-weight="normal" officeooo:rsid="0003f71a" officeooo:paragraph-rsid="0003f71a"/></style:style><style:style style:name="P4" style:family="paragraph" style:parent-style-name="Standard"><style:text-properties fo:font-variant="normal" fo:text-transform="none" fo:color="#2d3b45" style:font-name="LatoWeb" fo:font-size="7pt" fo:letter-spacing="normal" fo:font-style="normal" fo:font-weight="normal" officeooo:rsid="00041ba7" officeooo:paragraph-rsid="00041ba7"/></style:style><style:style style:name="P5" style:family="paragraph" style:parent-style-name="Standard"><style:text-properties fo:font-variant="normal" fo:text-transform="none" fo:color="#2d3b45" style:font-name="LatoWeb" fo:font-size="7pt" fo:letter-spacing="normal" fo:font-style="normal" fo:font-weight="normal" officeooo:rsid="0004da26" officeooo:paragraph-rsid="0004da26"/></style:style><style:style style:name="P6" style:family="paragraph" style:parent-style-name="Standard"><style:text-properties fo:font-variant="normal" fo:text-transform="none" fo:color="#2d3b45" style:font-name="LatoWeb" fo:font-size="7pt" fo:letter-spacing="normal" fo:font-style="normal" fo:font-weight="normal" officeooo:rsid="000624a3" officeooo:paragraph-rsid="000624a3"/></style:style><style:style style:name="T1" style:family="text"><style:text-properties officeooo:rsid="0003e931"/></style:style><style:style style:name="T2" style:family="text"><style:text-properties officeooo:rsid="0003f71a"/></style:style><style:style style:name="T3" style:family="text"><style:text-properties officeooo:rsid="00041ba7"/></style:style><style:style style:name="T4" style:family="text"><style:text-properties officeooo:rsid="0004da26"/></style:style><style:style style:name="T5" style:family="text"><style:text-properties officeooo:rsid="000624a3"/></style:style></office:automatic-styles><office:body><office:text><text:sequence-decls><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Illustration"/><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Table"/><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Text"/><text:sequence-decl text:display-outline-level="0" text:name="Drawing"/></text:sequence-decls><text:p text:style-name="P1">AESII #1. For the most part I agree with this statement. Humans are naturally greedy creatures who will seize as much  power as they can without consequences. In a position of power few people are able to check your decisions. In this environment most people to at least some extent will abuse their power.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P2"><text:span text:style-name="T1">#2 </text:span>Sadly I must agree with the statement for the simple reason that our entire law and society is based around this principle. Our entire civilization is based upon a social contract basically meaning that we all agree to not violate the laws so that if someone attempted to harm us we can be punished by the system. The idea of a court and police persecuting crime has not always  been the system rather we conducted personal vendettas. For example if you killed my brother I would kill yours and then you would seek revenge b killing my wife and so on. Our system is simply meant to dole out revenge without causing vendettas. For the simple reason that in order for our society to function revenge must be used as a system for enforcing justice.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P2"><text:span text:style-name="T1">#3 </text:span>I disagree with this statement for the reason that although this would be the ideal world people get away with misdeeds quite frequently. This is the world we live in and there i no system of karma enforcing our actions.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P1">#4 In order to answer this question we must first ask a question of semantics what does “must” mean in this context. If must mean if people do not confront injustice society will collapse or everyone will die then I must disagree with the statement for the simple reason people have not confronted social injustice multiple times in American history yet society doesn&apos;t collapse in these cases. If must means that if we do not confront social injustice with a considerable penalty inflicted to us that said injustice will continue to occur. One again history is behind me when I say I am forced to disagree with that statement as well. For example in Nazi Germany the average person did not confront the NSDAP yet they eventually fell. For another example in America the persecution of homosexuals was widespread throughout the nation but the average person regardless of their views did not help to defend the gays. However in time popular opinion <text:s text:c="2"/>swing around to supporting homosexuality so people jumped in the bandwagon but very few people staked a massive amount to cause that change to occur. Finally if the question perhaps meant must as should then I of course agree with the statement and people should do their best to confront social injustice when it arises. However, this sadly most of the time doesn’t occur with few people willing to devote very much to these issues but they are <text:span text:style-name="T2">usually</text:span> fixed <text:span text:style-name="T2">eventually</text:span> and society does continue to function.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P3">#5 I disagree with this statement. However I have little evidence to support this point simply because I cant relate to the existence. Also consider the fact it is quite possible nobody has discovered “the meaning of life” and the path to discovery of this is impossible to know.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P3">#6 While I would agree with this statement I must ask what is the difference between moral and physical courage. If physical courage is facing your fears due to a threat upon yourself and your primal instincts and mental courage is the ability to defy society, peer pressure and standing up for what’s right the answer is quite clear. We have had soldiers and warriors face their fears and go into combat in the millions however when there is a social injustice few are willing to defy the propaganda they are given and stand up for their beliefs for the quite simple reason that humans are biologically programed to want to please the crowd. The conclusion I have reached is that humans find “Moral Courage” to be more challenging is because it fights are most primal instincts. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P3">#7 I agree with this statements for the reasons <text:span text:style-name="T4">referrered</text:span> to in response #2. If people hold <text:span text:style-name="T3">vendettas</text:span> they will never end and everyone will suffer. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P3">#8 0, I believe it a persons choice to be able to remarry whenever they please. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P3">#9. I disagree with this statement for the simple reason that there has been no evidence in sufficient quantities to <text:span text:style-name="T3">justify</text:span> this belief <text:span text:style-name="T3">and because I do not believe in saying something just due to fate. So while it is “technically” possible ghosts exist I cannot support such a belief without solid proof. </text:span></text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#10 I disagree with this statement <text:s/>with only a few possible exceptions. Minors should have a right to privacy which spying on would violate and is not justified without considerable extenuating circumstances.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#11 I would agree with this statement however I would say that all humans act irrationally when it comes to love. The examples for this are countless and such primal emotions can quite often override logic causing people to do more irrational things.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#12 I would disagree with this statement in most circumstances for the simple reason that adults should take responsibility for themselves.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#13 Of course this statement is true boys are given more hands on contact and violent activities shooting sword fighting and so on while girls are usually treated more gently and in a more nurturing attitude. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#14/15 Disagree people should look out for themselves first before coming to the assistance of others.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#16 All people have a natural lust for power so I must agree with this statement although we can control this desire with effort. </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#17 I simply must agree with this statement for the reason that people naturally want a more import spouse and money is one way of expressing this. Of course money is not all that matters but practically everyone will take a rich person over a poor person if all their other attributes are the same.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P4">#18 Revenge is fairly common in day to day life although it <text:span text:style-name="T4">usually</text:span> on a very small scale. <text:span text:style-name="T4">As to rather revenge is justified the answer is quite occasionally yes. For example if someone routinely insulted me and I worked at a company he was applying for I feel that response is justified.</text:span></text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">#19 No</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">#20 I consider myself to be more of a thinker. My personality type is entp which is a good example of how I am a thinker rather than a doer.<text:line-break/></text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">Responses</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">Zoe </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">3. I disagree with this statement that while choices may always reflect on your future a negative action doesn&apos;t always reflect negatively on said future.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">16. While it is true that everyone is different some traits are uniform across humans and a desire for power is one of those traits. <text:span text:style-name="T5">Although</text:span> many people have turned down power when offered those people are fighting said desires and still seek power even in the form of material goods or money in one way or another.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">Wilder </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">7. Perhaps some people would survive unscathed but the quality of life would drop significantly.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P5">17. Although everyone is different the desire for a rich spouse does apply under a lust for power so everyone at least in some part of themselves unconsciously would rather have a more powerful i.e. rich spouse.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P6">Rebecca</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P6">5. This point has no reasoning so I cant present a counterargument I must simply disagree with you.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P6">16. <text:span text:style-name="T4">While it is true that everyone is different some traits are uniform across humans and a desire for power is one of those traits. </text:span>Although<text:span text:style-name="T4"> many people have turned down power when offered those people are fighting said desires and still seek power even in the form of material goods or money in one way or another.</text:span></text:p><text:p text:style-name="P6">Katelyn </text:p><text:p text:style-name="P6">6. I simply must disagree with you due to my own experiences and knowledge of society. However because the idea of physical/mental courage is so vague it is hard to give a counterargument for a question so badly stated.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P6">7. I think you are taking the question a bit too literally.</text:p><text:p text:style-name="P6"/></office:text></office:body></office:document-content>